We have main engine start, 4, 3, 2, 1, go!
You're a jerk, Tom!
Look Celia, we have to follow our passions.
You have your robotics and I just want to be awesome in space.
Why don't you just admit that you're freaked out by my robot hand?
I'm not freaked out, but it's...
Alright, fine. I'm freaked out.
I'm having nightmares that I'm being chased by these giant robotic claws.
Oh, what have I done? We're done!
Robot's memory synced and locked.
This is pretty freaky.
Shouldn't you be down there?
I heard you guys talking last night.
It's not my fault, you know?
It's not my fault.
Are you ready? Of course you're ready. You're a rock star.
How's it looking, Barley?
We should have about 10 minutes.
Well, that's perfect.
We're only one. All systems go!
Yeah, you.
We're only one.
We're only one. All systems go!
Yeah, you. Go! Go!
Move your asses! Go, go, go!
I love it!
Come on! Go!
That's nice.
Nothing to worry about. Tom...
Tom...
There she is.
Now, you love her.
She's your passion.
Be tender to her.
Be honest.
Be tender.
Remind her what love is.
I love you.
And... action!
Memory override in progress.
You're a jerk, Tom!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Look, Celia.
We have to follow our passions.
You have your robotics.
And I just want to be awesome in space.
Get her coming.
Two minutes left.
Two minutes.
Speed up, Tom!
Speed up, Celia!
Why don't you just admit that you're freaked out by my robot hand?
This is Celia.
I was young and a dick.
But there's no reason to destroy the world.
Why does she do this?
We already tried that one.
Come on!
Cut!
Whoa!
No!
You broke my heart.
I know.
You forgot me on Earth.
I should just crush you.
Just crush you!
I'm...
I'm sorry.
Do that, Lip.
Not my fault!
This time.
Quiet on set.
Round of times, round of times!
No!
You're a pain!
Emery overrated, 90%.
Captain, we have to abort!
The world's changed, Celia.
Maybe we can too.
Emery override complete!
You know...
There's a lesson to be learned from this.
Could have gone worse.
You're a pain!
To be continued...